<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<GDInfos>
    <GDInfo name="lng_cn" class="GDGameLanguage">
        <components>
            <comp class="CProperties">
                <display_name>简体中文</display_name>
                <language_code>zh-CN</language_code>
            </comp>
        </components>
        
        <!-- Guide Data -->
        <gstr name="GDGuideGroup.guidegroup_basics.name">基础</gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_intro.name">简介</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_intro.desc">            
热烈欢迎成为无限集团的先驱者！

当你在水银号基地设施中苏醒后，操作的第一步应该是进行全面诊断，并确保设施按预期计划运行。我们无限集团公司对自动化设施建设项目充满信心。

&lt;i&gt;&lt;size=12&gt;万一您丢失了本手册，我们建议您不要做任何对公司或其他员工不利的事情。同时要注意，如果你丢失了这本手册，那么也可能是任务没有成功，使这本手册和你的雇佣协议失效。
&lt;/size&gt;&lt;/i&gt; 

&lt;b&gt;**致命系统错误**&lt;/b&gt;

大量的错误日志表明，乘员没有在适当的时间被唤醒，导致水银号设施情况在过去几十年里严重恶化。

我们无限集团公司希望对由此造成的任何不便致以最诚挚的歉意。当你回到地球时，你可以采用诉讼的方式解决争议。


更新任务目标：

将殖民者从静滞休眠状态唤醒。注意，并非所有的殖民者都被记录在案。额外的休眠仓仍然可能保存完好，当然前提是要找到这些休眠仓。

生存下来，重建水银号设施。许多原始蓝图数据已被破坏。我们需要建造实验室工作站来研究新技术。


&lt;i&gt;&lt;size=12&gt;注意：虽然受伤和死亡不可避免，但我们绝不建议你这样做。你们都是无限集团公司大家庭的一员，我们不愿意失去你们。&lt;/size&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_mining.name">开采</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_mining.desc">
开采周边区域是获得各种材料和提供扩张空间的必要条件。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;基础开采&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
基础开采是为了清除直接限制移动的泥土或者矿石。这种类型的开采作业可以由人类殖民者和机器人完成。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;深层采掘&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
深层采掘是为了从矿石地块中采集矿物资源，只能由机器人组装器构建的深层钻机完成。深层采掘在采集完成后会自动填土覆盖坑洞。

从底部按钮栏选择采掘模式。拖动标记你想开采的区域。从已经标记的区域开始拖动覆盖已选择的区域，将取消选定状态。
        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_cropmanagement.name">作物管理</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_cropmanagement.desc">
各种各样的作物可以被种植用于产出食物和工业原料。有些作物需要发现物和经过研究才能种植。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;种子&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
作物需要种子才能种植。种子可以从已种植的作物、野生植物和探险过程中获得。当殖民者收获作物时能够同时采集，一单位种子。根据殖民者植物学技能级别，收获时有机会获得额外的种子。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;肥料&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
肥料是在肥料加工站制作的，施用肥料能加快植物生长。

选择作物后，肥料选项按钮将出现在作物生长进度条下方。选择使用肥料后，植物学家就会定时施用肥料。植物每个生长周期都会消耗一定的肥料，并且在每次收获后重新施用。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;气培农场&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
某些作物需要在气培农场种植。在这种设施中种植的作物生长得更快，抗病能力更强。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;枯萎&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
如果作物成熟后长时间不收获就就会进入枯萎状态。收割枯萎的作物只会产出种子。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;疾病&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
作物病害会随机发生。生病的作物应迅速清除，以避免蔓延到邻近的作物。
        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_crafting.name">制造</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_crafting.desc">
制造站台，类似于生物精炼器等，可以用来制造物品或者深加工各种材料。 

想要添加物品到制造队列中，可以选择相应的工作设施并点击“添加物品订单”按钮。 

   1. 从左边的配方列表中选择你想要制作的物品的配方
   2. 设定你希望制作的数量
   3. 点击应用

物品将会被添加到制造队列中。具有相应工作角色的殖民者将会尝试收集配方材料（如果可用的话），并在工作设施上制造物品。你可以点击制造队列中相应的物品图标来对制造信息进行修改。

&lt;b&gt;递送到存储区&lt;/b&gt;
如果选中此选项，殖民者将尝试在完成制作后将制作的物品运送到仓库。否则，如果还有其他需要制作的物品，他们会把制作好的物品就地放下，然后继续在机器上制作。

&lt;b&gt;低于X时制造&lt;/b&gt;
采用此种制造方式，如果存储区的物品大于或者等于设置数量时，殖民者将会“忽略”这个制造订单。
        </gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_objectplacement.name">建造物件</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_objectplacement.desc">                
为了加工材料、种植作物或保持殖民者情绪和健康，需要建造不同的机器和建筑。底部的按钮栏有几个可以选择放置的物体类别。当鼠标悬停在建造菜单中的一个项目上时，所需的材料、资源、地板类型和位置大小会显示在列表的右侧。有些物件在构建之前需要数据恢复或者进一步研究。

从建造列表中单击一个物件将关闭建造列表窗口并将该物件附加到鼠标指针上。将鼠标拖动到目标显示为绿色的合适位置，单击左键放置物件。

在放置物件之前，可以通过按“R”键来旋转物件方向。

在物体放置期间，物体占用空间保持可见状态。占用地块用不同的颜色来表示不同的状态，例如可通行（绿色），不可通行（红色）和避让方格（黄色）。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;红色方格&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
当放置该物件时，红色方格将变得无法通行。殖民者将无法通过这些方格。这些通常是被放置的机器或者建筑正下方的地块。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;绿色方格&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
对于这个物件，绿色方格是可通行的方格。绿色方格可以与其他物体的绿色方格区域重叠，但不能与红色或黄色方格重叠。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;黄色方格&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
殖民者会避开黄色方格。如果没有其他路径，殖民者仍然可以穿过这些方格，但他们更愿意选择另一条路线。

选择物件时，物件占用空间一直可见。一旦放置了物件，建造者将把所需的材料从存储区搬运到目标位置并建造物件。其他殖民者将在建造物体之前从建筑区域移走多余的物品。
        </gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_decor.name">装饰</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_decor.desc">            
装饰度代表了设施地块的吸引力，并对殖民者的压力数据有直接影响。工业机器、墙壁碎片和脏污物品等会产生负面效果。殖民者的压力会随着他们走过不同装饰度的区域而增加或减少。

你可以通过点击游戏界面右下角的装饰覆盖层按钮来查看装饰信息。红色区域为负相关，绿色区域为正相关，白色区表示没有影响。

装饰可以通过建造具有提高装饰度数据的物体，如墙壁，站立灯，长凳等来改善。
        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_rooms.name">房间</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_rooms.desc">            
房间的定义是由墙和门组成的少于500方格面积的封闭区域。房间的类型取决于放置在里面的大部分地板类型。如果大部分地板都是卧室地板，那这个房间就定义为卧室。

你可以使用小地图上方的房间区域显示模式按钮来切换房间能见度。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;装饰&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
房间的装饰度反映了它对殖民者的吸引力。这个数值可能会受到生产机械等物品的减值，以及受到良好装饰物品的增益。如果在装饰度较低的区域，殖民者可能会感到压力上升。要装饰的需求数量取决于房间的大小和房间里其他可能降低装饰度的物品。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;光照&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
光照对于提高殖民者的工作效率来说非常重要。可以通过在房间中添加光源物体来增加。所需的光照量取决于房间的大小。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;效率&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
房间的效率是由装饰度和照明量决定，影响殖民者的工作速度和工作成功几率。效率也会影响殖民者其他的行为，如睡眠和娱乐活动。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;房间影响&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
根据房间效率，工作成功几率最多增加20%。如果不是在合适的房间内进行工作，工作成功几率会降低10%。这只影响到可以在房间内进行的行动。某些活动例如，采矿就不受影响。

在房间内的工作设施能提高工作速度。当不在房间内时，工作设施的基本工作速度为25%。在房间时，基于房间效率，设施的工作速度可以提高到100%。

基于房间效率，研究站有最高可达50%的几率产生双倍研究点数。

根据房间效率，殖民者睡眠时间最多可以缩减25%。

根据房间的装饰，殖民者可以在睡觉或吃饭等活动中持续受到各种积极和消极的压力影响。

        </gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_research.name">研究项目</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_research.desc">            
完成研究项目将解锁各种新的建筑，食谱和更多其它有意思的事物。研究项目可以通过花费研究点数、技术片段或生物样本解锁。

研究点数是由一个作为科学家角色的殖民者在研究站生成的。通过增加研究站和科学家数量，可以更快地生成研究点。

技术碎片和生物样本可以从地表探险活动中找到。

在设施管理选项下方可以找到科研树选项，里面包含所有可以通过一定条件解锁的科研项目。 

红色部分的研究项目在完成先决研究项目后才能进行研究。一些研究项目还要求拥有某些发现物才能解锁。

        </gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_power.name">电力管理</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_power.desc">            
各种机器都需要电力。机器可以通过在自身和发电机之间建立电力线路来接收电力。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;燃料发电机&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
燃煤发电机是一种需要燃料的发电机。你可以通过点击发电机并查看它的信息来了解所需何种燃料。在发电机启用时，燃料的消耗速率是恒定的。

燃料将由担任搬运工角色的殖民者运送，并自动优先于其他运输工作。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;机械能&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
E.M.G.发电机（Emergency Mechanical Generator-应急机械发电机）可以将机械能转化为电能。需要技师定时补充势能才能正常工作。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;地表电力&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
安装在升降梯内部的电力线路可以让你访问从地面设施产生的电力。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;地热发电机&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
固定覆盖在地热出口，可以使用地热产出持续电力。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;电力存储&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
连接到电力网络的电池组可以储存电网中多余的电力。在你无法为机器产生够量电力时，剩余的电力缺口将由电池中存储的电力补齐，当然，前提是你要有储存有电力的电池连接在电网中。

        </gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_water.name">水资源管理</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_water.desc">            
很多机器都需要水，水是通过安装在水面的水泵提取的。将水泵放置在可行走的地面附近，方便殖民者建造。

耗水机器必须有从水泵到机器的水管连接。         
        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_watertrap.name">水阱笼</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_watertrap.desc">            
水阱笼会被动地从地下水源中收集材料和食物。采集速度受相邻水域格数影响。水阱笼不需要诱饵，但它的收集速度可以通过使用诱饵进一步提高。生物学家会把诱饵带到水阱笼里，并将其应用到水阱笼中。
        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_equipment.name">装备</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_equipment.desc">
装备物品可以由殖民者装备或安装到车辆和机器，以添加各种效果。装备物品可以制作或在科技箱中找到。殖民者、机器和车辆都有固定数量的装备槽。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;殖民者装备&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
殖民者装备可以通过选择一个殖民者并点击一个可用的装备槽来装备。在选择一个可用的装备项目后，殖民者将尝试去获得相应的物品，然后装备物品。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;机器装备&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
机器装备是通过选择机器和点击一个可用的设备槽来安装。在选择一个可用的装备项目后，建设者将尝试获取物品并安装在机器上。

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;载具装备&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
载具装备可以通过点击行星地图界面左侧车辆信息中的可用装备槽来安装。在选择一个可用的装备项目后，技工将把物品带到一个可用的容器中放置到载具仓。车辆必须停靠于载具仓安放装备，在安装好之前不能登车。

        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_caveins.name">塌方事件</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_caveins.desc">
塌方可能发生在距结构支撑物体5格以外的任何格子上。结构支撑包括天然土墙、矿堆、金属墙、门和电梯。在铺设了地板的地块上也可能发生塌方，所以建造的房间应该尽量不大于10x10的面积。

当塌方发生时，受影响的方格会坍塌，并堆满泥土或矿石。相邻的方格也有可能坍塌。
        </gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideGroup.guidegroup_colonists.name">殖民者</gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_attributes.name">特性</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_attributes.desc">            
Each colonist has three core attributes. Attributes determine possible job roles and job role success chance in addition to the effects below. Attributes can be modified by equipment items.
                        
&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Smarts&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Increases earned experience in Job Roles by 10% per point.
            
&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Muscles&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Determine inventory space by 10 per level. Colonists with 8 or above in muscles will no longer have a movement penalty applied when carrying items.

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Athletics&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Determines movement speed. Each colonist has a different base movement speed which is increased with each point in Athletics.
        </gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_needs.name">Needs</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_needs.desc">            
&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Health&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Colonist health is important to the survival of your colony. Colonists can lose health from various injuries while doing their job. Colonists are far less likely to be injured on the job if they are more skilled in that job. The Medi-Bed is used to treat patients which will restore their health and remove any ailments.


&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fatigue&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Colonists will get tired over time. While they can sleep on the floor, they will get greater benefit by sleeping in a bed.


&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hunger&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Like most biological lifeforms, colonists will need to consume food. Food is prepared at the cook station from grown crops.

Food items have two important attributes:

Satiation: This is the amount, in percent, of hunger that will be reduced when consuming this item. Better quality meals are more satiating than low quality or raw food item.

Nutrition: This affects the rate of change for the hunger meter. A higher nutrition percent will slow the change rate so that a colonist doesn’t become hungry again so soon. The applied nutrition value decays naturally over time.


&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stress&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Colonists work best in a calm and stress free environment. Negative facility decor, sleeping on the ground and other factors can cause colonists to become stressed. 

High stress will decrease the success chance of job actions which can result in various undesired results.

Each colonist also has a stress reaction Quirk. When a colonist reaches 100% stress they will act out depending on this quirk. You can view quirks in the colonist management screen or by selecting a colonist.
        </gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_jobroles.name">Job Roles</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_jobroles.desc">
Job roles determine what a colonist will and won’t do and can be changed at any time by clicking a job slot. Colonists can be assigned a primary, secondary and tertiary job role. The job slot also determines job priority. A job in the primary slot will have a higher priority than a job in the secondary slot.

Colonists gain experience as they perform tasks associated with a given job role. Once a colonist has generated enough experience they will gain a level in that job role. Higher level colonists will work faster and make fewer mistakes.
        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_schedules.name">Schedules</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_schedules.desc">
The schedules interface allows you to assign activities to your colonists per hour over a 24 hour period. Every colonist is assigned to at least one schedule. Additional schedules can be created and the activity hours can be changed by selecting the activity type and clicking the desired hour.

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Work&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
During work hours, colonists will perform work duties. Needs such as sleeping and eating will only occur if they become critical.

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sleep&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
The desire for sleep is increased during sleep hours. Colonists will head to bed during sleep hours if their sleep need is above 30%. Once a colonist is sleeping they will continue to sleep until fully rested, ignoring any other scheduled activities during this time.

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Recreation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
During recreation hours a colonist will handle their stress and hunger needs. The desire to eat is increased during this time and colonists will eat if their hunger is greater than 30%.

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Training&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
During training hours a colonist will perform attribute training activities such as working out in the gym or using the reading station.

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free Time&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Free time hours do not represent any specific activity. During this time colonists are able to perform any actions depending on their needs.

        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_training.name">Training</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_training.desc">
Colonists attributes and job roles can be trained using specialized equipment.

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Attributes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Colonists will train attributes at specific equipment, such as the treadmill, during designated training times. Training times can be configured using colonist schedules.

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Roles&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
The memory transfer station is used to transfer job experience from one colonist to another. The memory transfer station must be configured with a trainer, a trainee and what job to train.

Once set up, the trainer will begin transferring their job skill to the trainee for the assigned job role. Colonists will only use the memory transfer station during scheduled training hours. The trainee will gain job experience from the trainer until they are at the same level as the trainer.

        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_rostermanagement.name">Roster Management</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_rostermanagement.desc">
The colonist roster allows you to assign colonists that can work at the specified machine. Selecting a production machine and clicking the Manage Roster button will show a list of eligible colonists that can be assigned to that machine.

The roster will affect colonists in the following way:

        1. A colonist &lt;i&gt;will&lt;/i&gt; work at a machine with either an empty roster or a machine that has their name on it's roster list.
        2. A colonist &lt;i&gt;will not&lt;/i&gt; work at a machine that has a roster list and their name isn't on the list.
        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_robots.name">Robots</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_robots.desc">
Robots are a special type of colonist with limited job abilities. Robots won’t get stressed and don’t eat, but they do need to recharge their batteries at a recharge station. 

Additional robots, and robot types, can be built using the Robot Assembly machine, once the research for it has been performed. 
        </gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_quirks.name">Quirks</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_quirks.desc">            
Colonists may have some personality quirks that can positively or negatively affect both attributes and needs. Quirks can be viewed by selecting a colonist and clicking the Stats button in their info window. Hovering the mouse over a Quirk will show a tool-tip with additional information. 

Quirks are assigned randomly to a colonist upon colonist creation; this is true for cloned colonists as well. Quirks are a permanent element of that colonist.            
        </gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_ailments.name">Ailments</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_ailments.desc">            
Ailments can be contracted while a colonist is performing a job. A colonist with a higher job level in a certain job is less likely to receive an ailment. Ailments can affect colonist needs or attributes in a variety of ways depending on the nature of the ailment. Ailments may also directly impact that colonists health when they first receive the ailment. Ailments can be treated and removed at the Medi-Bed.            
        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideGroup.guidegroup_surfaceexploration.name">Planet Surface</gstr>
            
         <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_pois.name">Points Of Interest</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_pois.desc">
Points of Interest are explorable locations on the surface map. These are revealed as the map is explored. 

In order to explore Points Of Interest an expedition must be created. See the Expeditions section for more details.
        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_expeditions.name">Expeditions</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_expeditions.desc">
Expeditions allow colonists to venture out onto the surface of the planet to investigate points of interest. Points of interest can unlock new discoveries, resources and more.

The expedition list, on the planet map interface, is where you can create and monitor active expeditions. To form an expedition click the “+” button in the expedition list which will open the Create Expedition screen. 

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Vehicle Selection&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
While an expedition can travel on foot, a vehicle will provide increased speed and storage space on your journey.

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Manage Destinations&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Click the Manage Destinations button to select one or more Points Of Interest on the map to explore. Once the expedition party is formed they will automatically travel to each selected POI in turn and then return back to the facility to dock.

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Expedition Items&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Human colonists will require food while out exploring points of interest. After selecting your destinations the total distance will appear in the Expedition Details section. Be sure to add enough food so that the estimated food supply is equal to or greater than your estimated travel time.

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Colonist Selection&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Click the Manage Passengers button to select who will go on the expedition. Sending colonists with higher level job skills will increase your chance of succeeding at the points of interest. Selecting a point of interest on the map will provide information on any risk and what job roles are recommended.

Once an expedition has been created the colonists will bring supplies to the vehicle via the elevator or shipping container. Colonists will then board the vehicle. 

The expedition will automatically travel to each selected destination in turn and then return to the facility. When they arrive at a point of interest a window will appear with choices on completing the point of interest.
        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_surfaceconstruction.name">Surface Construction</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_surfaceconstruction.desc">
Buildings can be constructed on the planet surface. The build menu for surface buildings can be accessed by clicking the building button at the lower left of the Planet Map interface.

Buildings occupy a single tile and some buildings, such as the vehicle bay, must be placed adjacent to the primary facility. A selected structure will highlight green if it can be placed on a given tile.

        </gstr>
        
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_vehicleassembly.name">Vehicle Assembly</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_vehicleassembly.desc">
Vehicles are constructed at the Vehicle Bay. Materials are delivered to the vehicle bay using an available shipping container. Once a vehicle is constructed it is available in the vehicles section of the planet map interface.

Additional vehicle types can be unlocked through research.

        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_vehiclemanagement.name">Vehicle Management</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_vehiclemanagement.desc">
The vehicle management list, on the planet map interface, will show you the vehicles that you have constructed. When vehicles are docked you have the following button options:

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Embark&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Vehicles need to be embarked before they can explore and harvest on the surface. Clicking the Embark button will spawn the vehicle near your facility. 

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Deconstruct&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
This action will deconstruct the vehicle and half of the construction materials will be returned.
        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_vehicleactionbar.name">Vehicle Actions</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_vehicleactionbar.desc">
Selecting a vehicle, after it has been embarked, will show the vehicle action bar at the bottom of the planet map interface. The action bar also shows the current power and health of the vehicle. Actions require power to operate and will stop if the vehicle runs out of power. Vehicles will automatically recharge, using solar panels, during the day.

Most actions take a certain amount of time to perform. The action button, as well as the vehicle list, will show the action progress. Pressing an active action button will stop that action.
        </gstr>
            
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_surfaceresources.name">Surface Resources</gstr>
        <gstr name="GDGuideTopic.guidetopic_surfaceresources.desc">
Harvestable resources on the surface can be mined for additional materials. A surface resource deposit has a specific mineable resource and three possible depths. Deposit depths determine how much of a resource is available and what is required to mine it.

Surface deposits uncovered while exploring the map may also contain resources at subsurface and deep depths. The resource scanner is required to uncover hidden deposits on explored tiles that only contain subsurface and/or deep resources. Selecting a resource on the map will show what resources are available.

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Depth: Surface&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Can be mined by mining vehicles or mining platform
Uncovered while exploring the surface

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Depth: Subsurface&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Can be mined by mining vehicles or mining platform
Found while scanning using the resource scanner

&lt;size=20&gt;&lt;b&gt;Depth: Deep&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/size&gt;
Can only be mined by mining platform
Found while scanning using the resource scanner
        </gstr>
    </GDInfo>
</GDInfos>

